[](https://www.wilbooks.com/index.php?p=cart) Your cart is empty

 (610) 436-8755

 (610) 436-8755

* |
* |
* |
* |

[](https://www.wilbooks.com/index.php?p=cart) Cart is empty

MENU[](#)

Grade

Guided Reading Levels

Spanish Book Collections ▼

Spanish Books ▼

Series

Privacy Policy
==============

The following policy applies to Wilbooks.com and any other site owned and/or operated by or on behalf of Wilmington Book Source Inc. or any of its subsidiaries, that states that it is governed by this Privacy Policy and/or links to this Privacy Policy (the sites and entities collectively referred to herein as "Wilbooks.com" and/or "Wilbooks" respectively).

Wilbooks.com is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. This policy statement provides our visitors with an overview of the measures we have taken to provide a safe online environment.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, e-mail address, street address and phone number.

Wilbooks may collect online and use personally identifiable information from our visitors: (1) to process and fulfill orders for products; (2) in connection with contests, sweepstakes, games, surveys, forums, content submissions, classroom activities, our requests for suggestions and visitors' requests for information; and (3) to customize the content on our site for our visitors' current and future needs. In addition, this personally identifiable information may be used to provide our visitors, via e-mail or other means, information about materials and activities that may be of interest to them.

**NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AND THE USE OF COOKIE TECHNOLOGY**

We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called "cookies," and through our visitors' voluntary submissions to us and/or upon our request. By non-personally identifiable information, we are referring to information about our visitors' browsers (e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), operating systems (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), Internet service providers (e.g., AOL or NET.COM) and other similar information which we track in aggregate form. The non-personally identifiable information that we track is anonymous and will never be identified with or lead us back to any of our visitors.

Cookie technology helps us to know how many people visit us and where visitors go on our site. Cookies are small bits of information we send to your computer. Among other things, this non-personally identifiable information allows us to know which areas are favorites, which areas need a bit of improvement, or what technologies and Internet services are being used by our visitors so that we may continually improve our visitors' online experiences.

**USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the use of Wilbooks.com. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you're on the Web. When you are on our site, we have a back-end server that logs your computer's IP address. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements.

**SECURITY**

We will give out personal information as required by law, for example to comply with a court order or subpoena or to assist in criminal investigations. We may also give out personal information when we deem it advisable in order to protect the safety and security of our sites and visitors to our sites.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is August, 2005.

Most recently updated August, 2005.

Sign-up For Our Newsletter

Discounts, Promotions, and more!

ABOUT WILBOOKS

CONTACT WILBOOKS

1311 West Chester Pike  
West Chester, PA 19382  
Tel: 610-436-8755  
Fax: 610-436-6288  

Our Customers Say...

Many of my students are ELS students and they absolutely "hunger" for new information and have a strong desire to learn. These books are ideal and favorites with my students. They are the perfect size both physically to hold and also in text. Thank you for considering my application and sending me these books. They are a great addition to our classroom library! L. D., Second Grade Teacher

Copyright 2024 Wilbooks. All Rights Reserved. [Site Map](https://www.wilbooks.com/site-map) | [Terms + Conditions](https://www.wilbooks.com/terms-conditions) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.wilbooks.com/privacy-policy)
